I'll show you how we can add breakpoints in our code. Go ahead and
click on the screen bug icon, to attach the debugger.
We'll go to the Settings menu. In the SettingsActivity I'm going to add two
breakpoints, in the onPreferenceChange method. I'm going to add a breakpoint at
line 59 in the case of a ListPreference when it's about to set the summary. I'm
also going to add a breakpoint at line 63, when it's not a ListPreference and it
sets the summary. Let's go into the app to try it out. Tap on the Location and
change the postal code. If you hit OK, then it triggers the breakpoint to
stop at right here. These are the values of the variables at this time.
And we see the new postal code here. You can step over or into the method for
more details. Or you can hit Play to continue. Or Stop to stop the debugger.
Let's hit Play to continue. And then we see that the [UNKNOWN] has been
updated to the, the preference summary, is the new postal code. Let's try it for
Temperature Units. They tap here, and then select Imperial.
It triggers this breakpoint in the ListPreference case. We hit Play to continue,
and then we see that, Imperial is now the preference summary.